<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=12] -->
    <string name="app_name">Go Carlsbad</string>

    <!-- Section name for attractions [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="section_attractions">Attractions</string>

    <!-- Section name for attractions [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="section_restaurants">Restaurants</string>

    <!-- Section name for attractions [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="section_beaches">Beaches</string>

    <!-- Section name for attractions [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="section_shopping">Shopping</string>

    <!-- Section name for attractions [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="section_sports">Sports</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Legoland -->
    <string name="legoland_name">LEGOLAND California Resort</string>
    <string name="legoland_address">One LEGOLAND Drive, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="legoland_description">LEGOLAND® California Resort has more than 60 rides, shows
        and attractions including the exciting new LEGO® NINJAGO® World! Ninja practice at special
        training areas to become masters of the ancient art of Spinjitzu. All that training gets put
        to the test on the stunning new LEGO NINJAGO The Ride. This interactive, cutting-edge,
        technological marvel allows riders to control animated fireballs, lightning, shockwaves and
        ice. Harness the power of the elements to defeat the Great Devourer and collect points for
        ninja status! But that’s not all that’s new for 2016. Emmet, Wyldstyle, Benny, MetalBeard
        and UniKitty star in The LEGO® Movie™ 4D A New Adventure.\n\nOur heroes, along with the
        audience, take a trip to a theme park and wind up in an incredible adventure they never
        expected. It’s an all-new, totally original, never seen before 4D movie and it’s only at
        LEGOLAND. Inside LEGOLAND, you can enter a world of knights and princesses to conquer the
        Dragon Coaster. Kids can drive their own cars at Driving School. Make new friends at LEGO
        Friends Heartlake City. The Resort is also home to the LEGOLAND Water Park featuring the
        LEGO Legends of CHIMA™ Water Park. Right nelegolaxt door is the wonder-filled SEA LIFE® Aquarium.
        There’s so much to do, you’ll want to spend the night. The amazing LEGOLAND Hotel has 250
        rooms and it’s packed with LEGO features.\n\nLEGOLAND California is open daily spring and
        summer and closed select Tuesdays and Wednesdays during the fall and winter.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for LEGOLAND Water Park -->
    <string name="waterpark_name">LEGOLAND Water Park</string>
    <string name="waterpark_address">One LEGOLAND Drive, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="waterpark_description">LEGOLAND California Resort features the world’s first
        LEGOLAND Water Park. The centerpiece is a 45-foot-tall tower designed to immerse children in
        the creative world of LEGO. The Water Park also features more than 20 LEGO models including
        giant LEGO friends who splash or spray water on guests, two sandy beach wading areas, retail
        shops and snack carts.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Sea Life Aquarium -->
    <string name="sealife_name">SEA LIFE Aquarium</string>
    <string name="sealife_address">One LEGOLAND Drive, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="sealife_description">Merlin’s SEA LIFE® attractions are an ideal, friendly and
        authoritative guide to the last great frontier…the seas and oceans of the world and their
        myriad mysterious and amazing inhabitants. Unrivalled display technology, biological
        expertise and entertainment skills combine to provide seamless journeys through US and
        tropical waters, and astonishing close encounters with everything from humble shrimps and
        starfish to seahorses, sharks and stingrays.Tamarack Surf Beach 3900 Carlsbad Boulevard,
        Carlsbad, CA 92008SEA LIFE® is designed to be a child’s first interactive guide to the life
        of the sea, combining active, hands-on learning with fascinating educational talks, and
        opportunities to have up close and personal encounters with a variety of sea creatures. A
        visit to SEA LIFE® is an experience like no other!</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Flower Fields -->
    <string name="flowerfields_name">The Flower Fields at Carlsbad Ranch</string>
    <string name="flowerfields_address">5704 Paseo del Norte, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="flowerfields_description">The Flower Fields at Carlsbad Ranch is a fifty-acre
        dazzling rainbow of beautiful ranunculus flowers set on a hillside overlooking the striking
        Carlsbad, California coastline. The outdoor space is idyllic for planning weddings, events
        and corporate gatherings held among the lush gardens, or you may choose to nestle indoors in
        our 200-seat Paul Ecke Jr. Barn for special occasions!\n\nWe invite you to enjoy our tractor
        driven wagon rides, our 1500 square foot greenhouse filled with world famous Ecke
        poinsettias, the sweet pea maze, Santa’s playground, an orchid greenhouse, and many themed
        gardens. Throughout the season we also hold special events and music designed for visitors
        of all ages that is included with admission. Picnic tables are on site and parking is free.
        \n\nLocated in North San Diego County, a region with a rich history of growing flowers going
        back to the 1940’s. The Flower Fields at Carlsbad Ranch is located less than one half-mile
        from the ocean, within five minutes of several prominent hotels and restaurants, and a short
        drive from two international airports (San Diego and Orange County).</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Gemological Institute of America (GIA) -->
    <string name="gia_name">Gemological Institute of America (GIA)</string>
    <string name="gia_address">5345 Armada Drive, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="gia_description">Established in 1931 by Robert M. Shipley, the Gemological
        Institute of America (GIA) in Carlsbad, CA, is the world’s leading authority and educator on
        diamonds, colored stones, and pearls.\n\nVisitors to the GIA headquarters have an
        opportunity to learn about the Institute’s world-renowned educational programs, explore gem
        and jewelry exhibits, visit the Richard T. Liddicoat Gemological Library &amp; Information
        Center and see the Tower of Brilliance; the world’s largest crystal octahedron.\n\nThe
        center is dedicated to educating, researching and understanding gemstones, and protecting
        potential jewelry buyers by setting quality standards on a global level.\n\nTo schedule and
        individual or group tour to the Gemological Institute of America, please email or call
        800-421-7250 ext 4116 or 760-603-4116.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Museum of Making Music -->
    <string name="musicmuseum_name">Museum of Making Music</string>
    <string name="musicmuseum_address">5790 Armada Drive, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="musicmuseum_description">The Museum of Making Music is a fun and informative
        museum that exists to inspire visitors to interactively discover the history of making
        music, musical instruments and products. At the museum you will travel through time, from
        1900 to today, exploring the connections among people, instruments, and the music we make…
        and make some music of your own! A vibrant concert series is ongoing throughout the
        year!</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Green Dragon Tavern & Museum  -->
    <string name="dragontavern_name">Green Dragon Tavern &amp; Museum </string>
    <string name="dragontavern_address">6115 Paseo Del Norte, Carlsbad, CA 92011</string>
    <string name="dragontavern_description">Green Dragon Tavern &amp; Museum is the latest major
        attraction to open in the Carlsbad, CA, area. The 22,000 sq. ft. space will feature a
        museum, restaurant, tavern, coffee house and meeting space. GDTM creates a welcoming
        atmosphere for celebrating, remembering and honoring early American history, our founding
        fathers and their many contributions to our past and modern day society. Offering
        complimentary admission, the Green Dragon Museum will house documents from the Colonial and
        Revolutionary War-eras and will provide individuals of all ages with an opportunity to
        further appreciate our country’s rich history. Additionally, chef de cuisine Greg Krohl has
        created a menu for Green Dragon Tavern &amp; Museum that reflects “old world” meets “new
        world” cuisine and features all locally farmed and sustainable ingredients. Diners will have
        a chance to experience Chef Krohl’s skillful, culinary masterpieces while enjoying the
        atmosphere, ambiance and historical charm of Green Dragon Tavern &amp; Museum.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Leo Carrillo Ranch & Historic Park -->
    <string name="leocarillo_name">Leo Carrillo Ranch &amp; Historic Park</string>
    <string name="leocarillo_address">6200 Flying Leo Carillo Lane, Carlsbad, CA 92009</string>
    <string name="leocarillo_description">Once part of the original 2,538 acre working rancho and
        vacation retreat of Leo Carrillo (who acted in almost 100 films from 1927 to 1950 and
        co-starred in the TV series The Cisco Kid) the historic Leo Carrillo Ranch is an
        extraordinary educational and recreational resource.\n\nThe City of Carlsbad has stabilized,
        preserved and restored many of the buildings on this 27 acre parcel. Historic structures at
        Rancho Carrillo Carlsbad include a visitors center, hand-crafted adobe buildings, hacienda,
        reflecting pool, cabana, cantina, carriage house tack shed, stable, barn and foundry and
        equipment shed. It can be found on the Citywide Trails System 4-mile long Rancho Carrillo
        Trail. Self-guided walking tours and 13-minute introductory film give an overview. Guided
        90-minute walking tours are offered on Saturdays.\n\nLeo Carrillo Ranch is a 27-acre
        historical park with irregular earthen and paved surfaces, including without limitations,
        stairs and trails. It is recommended that visitors wear appropriate shoes for the uneven
        terrain within this historic park.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Karl Strauss Brewing Company -->
    <string name="karlstrauss_name">Karl Strauss Brewing Company</string>
    <string name="karlstrauss_address">5801 Armada Drive, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="karlstrauss_description">Chain brewpub offering American bar food with a gourmet
        twist alongside house-brewed craft ales.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Ignite Bistro & Wine Spot -->
    <string name="ignitebistro_name">Ignite Bistro &amp; Wine Spot</string>
    <string name="ignitebistro_address">6996 El Camino Real, Carlsbad, CA 92009</string>
    <string name="ignitebistro_description">Seafood, wood-fired pizza &amp; steaks paired with a
        sizable wine list as well as garden patio seating.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Pisco Rotisserie & Cevicheria -->
    <string name="pisco_name">Pisco Rotisserie &amp; Cevicheria</string>
    <string name="pisco_address">5970 Avenida Encinas, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="pisco_description">Modern &amp; traditional Peruvian dishes served in a cheerful
        space decked out with paper parasols.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Casa De Bandini Mexican Restaurant -->
    <string name="casadebandini_name">Casa De Bandini Mexican Restaurant</string>
    <string name="casadebandini_address">1901 Calle Barcelona, Carlsbad, CA 92009</string>
    <string name="casadebandini_description">Festive eatery serves classic Mexican cuisine in a
        colorful dining room with roving mariachi bands.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Nozomi Japanese Fusion -->
    <string name="nozomi_name">Nozomi Japanese Fusion</string>
    <string name="nozomi_address">3050 Pio Pico Dr, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="nozomi_description">Serving Asian fusion plates &amp; sushi amid a zen-like
        atmosphere complete with bamboo &amp; waterfalls.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Pizza Port Brewery & Restaurant -->
    <string name="pizzaport_name">Pizza Port Brewery &amp; Restaurant</string>
    <string name="pizzaport_address">571 Carlsbad Village, Carlsbad, CA 92008\n2730 Gateway Road,
        Carlsbad, CA 92009</string>
    <string name="pizzaport_description">You can enjoy a cool brew and a Pizza Port special slice in
        the (nearly always) perfect Carlsbad weather. As their saying goes “Good food and good beer
        bring good cheer!” </string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Buca di Beppo Carlsbad -->
    <string name="bucadibeppo_name">Buca di Beppo Carlsbad</string>
    <string name="bucadibeppo_address">1921 Calle Barcelona, Carlsbad, CA 92009</string>
    <string name="bucadibeppo_description">Chain serving family-style Italian fare in a kitschy
        setting featuring red-&amp;-white tablecloths.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Campfire -->
    <string name="campfire_name">Campfire</string>
    <string name="campfire_address">2725 State St, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="campfire_description">Buzzy indoor/outdoor locale serving wood-fired American fare
        cocktails amid camping decor.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Canyons Restaurant -->
    <string name="canyons_name">Canyons Restaurant</string>
    <string name="canyons_address">5800 The Crossings Dr., Carlsbad, CA, 92008</string>
    <string name="canyons_description">Castlelike venue at The Crossings with fine American eats &amp;
        a patio overlooking the golf course.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Cicciotti’s Trattoria Italiana & Seafood -->
    <string name="ciciottis_name">Cicciotti’s Trattoria Italiana &amp; Seafood</string>
    <string name="ciciottis_address">595 Grand Avenue, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="ciciottis_description">Rustic-chic kitchen in a converted garage, featuring pizzas
        &amp; hearty Italian meat &amp; seafood entrees.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for South Ponto Beach -->
    <string name="ponto_name">South Ponto Beach</string>
    <string name="ponto_address">Carlsbad Blvd north of La Costa Blvd, Carlsbad, CA</string>
    <string name="ponto_description">South Ponto Beach is a rare gem in that it is one of the widest
        beaches in the county and exists in an undeveloped area. Coast Hwy 101 hugs the shoreline
        here, with Batiquitos Lagoon on the other side of the highway. The beach is a popular family
        destination, and only one of the few beaches in the area that has public restrooms and
        showers. South Ponto Beach is secluded with its high sand dunes and tends to have a lot of
        polished stones washed up during the winter time.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Tamarack-State Beach -->
    <string name="tamarack_name">Tamarack-State Beach</string>
    <string name="tamarack_address">Carlsbad Blvd &amp; Tamarack Ave, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="tamarak_description">Carlsbad State Beach, also known as Tamarack Beach, stretches
        from the warm water jetties, just south of Tamarack Avenue, to Frazee Beach, near Carlsbad
        Village Drive.\n\nThe beach is ideal for the family and kids, the state beach offers
        swimming, surfing, scuba diving, kayaking, windsurfing, fishing and beachcombing. Many
        people fish off the Carlsbad jetties, both near Tamarack beach and the campgrounds.\n\nThe
        Carlsbad Seawall, a paved 4-mile walking path along the coast, extends from Carlsbad Village
        drive to Cannon). The seawall separates The beach from Coast Hwy 101, where you can find
        people walking, jogging, and cycling. All throughout the day you can see joggers, walkers,
        cyclists and roller-bladers cruising up and down the path. This is definitely an active
        city.\n\nCarlsbad State Beach offers an amazing view of the sunset. Every night people
        gather at the north end of the beach, on the bluff (towards the village) to watch the sun
        sink into the Pacific Ocean. The palisades and walkway atop the Seawall is another romantic
        spot for watching the sunset and enjoying the ocean view.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for South State Beach -->
    <string name="statebeach_name">South State Beach</string>
    <string name="statebeach_address">7106 Carlsbad Blvd, Carlsbad, CA 92011</string>
    <string name="statebeach_description">South Carlsbad State Beach extends from Palomar Airport
        oad to La Costa Ave. Unlike Carlsbad State Beach to the north, this beach has few amenities,
        except for the campgrounds, and is rather remote. Popular activities include swimming,
        surfing, skin diving, fishing and picnicking, and sunbathing. Good quality sand makes this
        beach ideal for walking and jogging.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for North Carlsbad Beaches -->
    <string name="northbeach_name">North Carlsbad Beaches</string>
    <string name="northbeach_address">2499 Ocean Street, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="northbeach_description">These beaches stretch from Oceanside border to Pine Ave,
        near Carlsbad Village. Jointly owned by the state and the coastal property owners along that
        stretch, north Carlsbad beaches are open to the public. However, they do not have any
        lifeguard services, restrooms, showers or other amenities. These north beaches can be
        accessed at Carlsbad Village Drive, Grand Avenue, Christiansen Way, Beech Ave and Rue des
        Chateaux.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Terramar Beach -->
    <string name="terramar_name">Terramar Beach</string>
    <string name="terramar_address">5399 County Highway S21, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="terramar_description">Terramar is located South of the Carlsbad Power plant and
        North of Palomar Airport Road. This quaint and somewhat hidden beach is a great spot for
        local surfers to catch a wave. There are no public restrooms at the beach or within walking
        distance of the beach. Though there aren’t lifeguards on duty, lifeguards do patrol the area
        in their vehicles.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Carlsbad Premium Outlets -->
    <string name="premiumoutlets_name">Carlsbad Premium Outlets</string>
    <string name="premiumoutlets_address">5620 Paseo del Norte, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="premiumoutlets_description">Savvy shoppers know to visit Carlsbad Premium Outlets
        when they’re in North San Diego County. This beautiful outdoor shopping center in Carlsbad
        offers an exciting collection of 90 designer and name-brand outlet stores including Barneys
        New York Warehouse, Coach, Elie Tahari, Kate Spade New York, Michael Kors, Nike Factory
        Store and many more, all offering savings of 25% to 65% every day.\n\nConveniently located
        near LEGOLAND California Resort, the beautiful beaches and campgrounds of South Carlsbad,
        the outlets offers something for everyone in your group. Enjoy the sunshine and shopping,
        and be sure to stop into one of the many restaurants conveniently located throughout the
        center. Whether you’re in the mood for a quick snack or a leisurely meal, you will also find
        an array of delicious dining options at the center.\n\nLocated just east of I-5 off Palomar
        Airport Road, Carlsbad Premium Outlets is the premier shopping destination in North San
        Diego County.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for The Forum At Carlsbad -->
    <string name="theforum_name">The Forum At Carlsbad</string>
    <string name="theforum_address">1923 Calle Barcelona, Carlsbad, CA 92013</string>
    <string name="theforum_description">The Forum Carlsbad is one of these “new-style” outdoor
        malls. At the Forum Carlsbad, you’ll find elegant architecture punctuated by decorative
        accents. Flowers in a range of pretty pastel colors fill festive ceramic flower pots. Trees
        and greenery grow in the center’s medians and along the sidewalks. Brilliantly-hued
        umbrellas shade guests relaxing as they dine in outdoor patio settings. Gentle breezes
        caress shoppers strolling along from one store to another.\n\nThis pleasant setting is a
        great place to shop, enjoy a meal, or just drink-in the atmosphere. When you’re weary of the
        hustle &amp; bustle of larger malls in the area, the Forum Carlsbad makes a fun place to
        head for a change of pace to relax &amp; unwind.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for The Shoppes at Carlsbad -->
    <string name="theshoppes_name">The Shoppes at Carlsbad</string>
    <string name="theshoppes_address">2525 El Camino Real #100, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="theshoppes_description">We see more than a mall. We see the center of a community.
        At The Shoppes at Carlsbad, we are committed to creating a mall experience that meets the
        ever-changing needs of our community.\n\nThe Shoppes at Carlsbad is undergoing a multi-phase
        renovation of its interiors and streetscapes to transform and enhance the shopping, dining,
        and entertainment destination to better serve Carlsbad residents, nearby Oceanside
        community, and the greater North County San Diego area. The Shoppes at Carlsbad’s modernized
        new design aesthetic will capture Carlsbad’s beach-centric lifestyle with the addition of
        contemporary coastal living-inspired architectural elements, including weather wood accents,
        natural stone, woven textiles and native plants</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Carlsbad Village Art & Antique Mall -->
    <string name="antiquemall_name">Carlsbad Village Art &amp; Antique Mall</string>
    <string name="antiquemall_address">2752 State Street, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="antiquemall_description">Carlsbad Village Art and Antique Mall is located in
        downtown Carlsbad. It offers art, antiques, decor and gifts. Customers have the option buy,
        sell, consign, or auction. Estate liquidations also happen here. There is a little something
        for everyone and every taste from Asian antiques to European, Californian and American
        fferings. Pricing is reasonable and the dealers are always willing to make a deal.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Village Faire -->
    <string name="villagefaire_name">Village Faire</string>
    <string name="villagefaire_address">300 Carlsbad Village Drive, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="villagefaire_description">Welcome to the Village Faire Shopping Center, located in
        the heart of the historic village of Carlsbad, California near the corner of Carlsbad
        Boulevard and Carlsbad Village Drive.\n\nWith its New England-style architecture with a
        Caribbean flare, this enclave of over 33 restaurants, shops and services surrounds a
        pleasant fountain courtyard with plenty of benches for relaxing.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Carlsbad Village Association -->
    <string name="villageassoc_name">Carlsbad Village Asociation</string>
    <string name="villageassoc_address">2579 State Street, Suite B, Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="villageassoc_description">The Carlsbad Village Association began in the late 70’s
        as the Village Merchants Association and was established as a non-profit corporation,
        Carlsbad Village Business Association in 1994. From the beginning its purpose was to promote
        and support the businesses located in the vicinity of Carlsbad Village.\n\nIn July of 2009,
        The Carlsbad Village Business Association and the Carlsbad Village Improvement Partnership
        consolidated their two boards to create the Carlsbad Village Association. The CVA’s goals
        have broadened to reach the community at large in an effort to create a true community
        through business and residential involvement.\n\nCVA membership is open to a wide and
        diverse population, both business and residential. Most businesses in the Village are
        owner-operated, creating a more personal and inviting experience every time you visit. Warm
        smiles and friendly service will always welcome you to Carlsbad Village.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Carlsbad Marathon -->
    <string name="marathon_name">Carlsbad Marathon</string>
    <string name="marathon_address">6116 Innovation Way, Carlsbad, CA 92009</string>
    <string name="marathon_description">Carlsbad is a winter marathon and half marathon unlike any
        other. From our ideal weather conditions to our spectacular coastal course, our award
        winning event will wow you.\n\nOur 26 fully staffed course support stations, continuous
        entertainment and unsurpassed volunteer support are just a few of our outstanding features.
        We also offer each participant a technical fabric shirt, goodie bag, spectacular finisher’s
        medal and more. Our boutique-style event with an emphasis on quality and individual service
        sets us apart from the mega marathons.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Carlsbad Triathlon -->
    <string name="carlsbadtriathlon_name">Carlsbad Triathlon</string>
    <string name="carlsbadtriathlon_address">Tamarack Surf Beach\n3900 Carlsbad Boulevard,
        Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="carlsbadtriathlon_description">Carlsbad Triathlon ranks in the world’s top 5
        longest running triathlons. It is a sprint distance race, consisting of a 1K open-water
        ocean swim, 25K bike and 5K run. The course begins at Tamarack Surf Beach, and follows the
        coastline of Carlsbad, past our scenic beaches, lagoons and wildlife preserve. It boasts an
        ocean swim, a rolling bike course and a smooth run for the finish.\n\nThis race is for
        everybody from first-timers to the elites, and their friends and family! The race begins
        with a 1K open-water ocean swim, which is well marked with buoys, followed by a 25K bike
        course and 5K run that takes you along the coastline. The roads are wide and completely
        closed to traffic—very safe! The course is mostly flat with a couple of rolling areas.
    </string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Kia Classic -->
    <string name="kiaclassic_name">Kia Classic</string>
    <string name="kiaclassic_address">7100 Aviara Resort Drive, Carlsbad, CA 921011</string>
    <string name="kiaclassic_description">The KIA Classic is a four-day, 72-hole stroke play
        competition, preceded by a one-day, 18-hole Pro-Am and will be attended by 144 LPGA
        professionals. The tournament is in March at the beautiful Aviara Golf Club.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Carlsbad Grand Prix -->
    <string name="grandprix_name">Carlsbad Grand Prix</string>
    <string name="grandprix_address">Armada Drive Carlsbad, CA 92008</string>
    <string name="grandprix_description">The Carlsbad Grand Prix is a cycling criterium circuit
        along a 0.9 mile closed course that loops through Armada Drive and Fleet Street in Carlsbad.
        The finish boasts a sweeping view of the Pacific Ocean. This full day of races features more
        than 700 junior, amateur, and professional cyclists competing in timed races for prizes
        and/or cash in front of 2,000 spectators. Additionally, the Kids Fun Race will host over 100
        entrants. Races start at 7:00am and finish in the late afternoon. Spectating and expo is
        free and open to the public.</string>

    <!-- Attraction info for Carlsbad 5000 -->
    <string name="carlsbad5000_name">Carlsbad 5000</string>
    <string name="carlsbad5000_address">9477 Waples St., Ste. 150, San Diego, CA 92121</string>
    <string name="carlsbad5000_description">The Carlsbad 5000 features a fast and fun seaside course
        where 16 world records have been set. Both rookie runners and serious speedsters alike enjoy
        running or walking in one of seven people’s races.\n\nEach year approximately 11,500
        spectators and 8,500 participants from all over the United States and many foreign
        countries. The Junior Carlsbad race annually draws 6,500 spectators and more than 3,500
        participants ages 12 and under.</string>

    <!-- Variables Items -->
    <string name="name_var">placeName</string>
    <string name="address_var">placeAddress</string>
    <string name="desc_var">placeDescription</string>
    <string name="img_var">placeImage</string>
    <string name="more">More info</string>
    <string name="site_var">placeSite</string>
    <string name="loc_var">placeLocation</string>
</resources>
